 practice_questions = [
  {
    Sentence : "The children ran outside to",
    Completion: "play",
    Left_or_Right: "left",
    Question: "The children are playing.",
    Correct_Response: "y"
  }]
  /*{
    Sentence_Stem : "On Valentine's Day the woman received a single red",
    Completion: "rose",
    Left_or_Right: "right",
    Question: "The woman got a daisy.",
    Correct_Response: "n"
  },
  {
    Sentence_Stem : "The princess would someday become a",
    Completion: "queen",
    Left_or_Right: "left",
    Question: "The princess will be a princess forever.",
    Correct_Response: "n"
  },
  {
    Sentence_Stem : "The Parkers' baby could already say three",
    Completion: "words",
    Left_or_Right: "right",
    Question: "The baby is mute.",
    Correct_Response: "n"
  },
  {
    Sentence_Stem : "The grandmother left everything to her son in her",
    Completion: "will",
    Left_or_Right: "left",
    Question: "The son received his grandmother's belongings.",
    Correct_Response: "y"
  },
  {
    Sentence_Stem : "The fluffy white clouds are high up in the",
    Completion: "sky",
    Left_or_Right: "right",
    Question: "The sky is cloudless.",
    Correct_Response: "n"
  },
  {
    Sentence_Stem : "To promote their album the band went on",
    Completion: "tour",
    Left_or_Right: "left",
    Question: "The band made an album.",
    Correct_Response: "y"
  },
  {
    Sentence_Stem : "Katie put the flowers in an expensive",
    Completion: "vase",
    Left_or_Right: "right",
    Question: "The vase is pretty pricey.",
    Correct_Response: "y"
  },
  {
    Sentence_Stem : "The maid dusted the books on the",
    Completion: "shelf",
    Left_or_Right: "left",
    Question: "The maid is slacking off.",
    Correct_Response: "n"
  },
  {
    Sentence_Stem : "The birthday card was funny and made me",
    Completion: "laugh",
    Left_or_Right: "right",
    Question: "The birthday card made me happy.",
    Correct_Response: "y"
  }
];*/